=I Want to Resign Every Single Day=
= أريد أن أستقيل كل يوم =
=Episode 16=
= الحلقة 16 =
Jin Shi'an!
جين شيآن!
Jin Shi'an.
جين شيان.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
Amb...
مع...
Amb... Amb...
مع مع...
Hang in there, Boss.
تشبث هناك ، بوس.
The loop will be over at midnight.
الحلقة ستنتهي عند منتصف الليل.
One minute to go.
يتبقى دقيقة واحدة.
Amb...
مع...
(Right.)
(الصحيح.)
(We'll try if kissing can end the loop.)
(سنحاول إذا كان التقبيل يمكن أن ينهي الحلقة.)
Hang in there.
أصبر.
I'll kiss you at midnight.
سوف أقبلك في منتصف الليل.
Twenty seconds to go.
عشرون ثانية للذهاب.
(Don't kiss me. If the loop is over, I'll die.)
(لا تقبلني. إذا انتهت الحلقة ، سأموت).
Why are you so impatient?
لماذا أنت غير صبور جدا؟
Fine. Here I go.
بخير.  ها أنا ذا.
(Five, four, three, two, one.)
(خمسة أربعة ثلاثة اثنان واحد.)
Amb...
مع...
Amb... Amb...
مع مع...
(Luckily, the loop isn't over.)
(لحسن الحظ ، لم تنته الحلقة.)
Instead of saving my life,
بدلاً من إنقاذ حياتي ،
Secretary Bai even tried to kill me.
حتى أن السكرتير باي حاول قتلي.
How did you get in?
كيف تحصل في؟
I'm very disappointed, Secretary Bai.
أشعر بخيبة أمل كبيرة ، الوزير باي.
When I was so badly wounded,
عندما أصبت بجروح بالغة ،
you kissed me, trying to end the loop.
لقد قبلتني ، في محاولة لإنهاء الحلقة.
How malicious!
كم هو ضار!
But last night, you pouted
لكن الليلة الماضية ، عابست
and urged me to kiss you.
وحثني على تقبيلك.
I said, amb... amb...
قلت ، مع ... مع ...
I wanted you to get an ambulance.
أردت أن تحصل على سيارة إسعاف.
Amb...
مع...
I didn't quite understand then.
لم أفهم تمامًا بعد ذلك.
And the loop was going to start.
وستبدأ الحلقة.
Time was running out.
كان الوقت ينفد.
It was the ambulance's problem.
كانت مشكلة سيارة الإسعاف.
But you had a big attitude problem.
لكن كان لديك مشكلة كبيرة في الموقف.
Jin Shi'an, I...
جين شيان ، أنا ...
Jin Shi'an?
جين شيان؟
You saved my life.
أنت أنقذت حياتي.
So, I conceded in the previous loops.
لذلك ، اعترفت في الحلقات السابقة.
But you shouldn't ask too much.
لكن لا يجب أن تطلب الكثير.
Think of it this way.
أعتقد أنه من هذا الطريق.
We're in a time loop.
نحن في حلقة زمنية.
I don't get paid.
أنا لا أتقاضى راتبي.
We're friendly and equal.
نحن ودودون ومتساوون.
You're not a boss.
أنت لست رئيسًا.
Fine.
بخير.
Let's get even when the loop is over.
دعنا حتى عندما تنتهي الحلقة.
OK.
نعم.
By the way,
على فكرة،
when the Maintenance Department fixed the elevator,
عندما أصلحت إدارة الصيانة المصعد ،
they found it was tampered with.
وجدوا أنه تم العبث به.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Wait.
انتظر.
What?
ماذا؟
I suddenly remember
أتذكر فجأة
the noise I heard on the phone
الضوضاء التي سمعتها في الهاتف
was the falling of the elevator.
كان سقوط المصعد.
Are you saying
هل تقول
every time I called you,
في كل مرة اتصلت بك
I was in an elevator accident?
كنت في حادث مصعد؟
Yes.
نعم.
It didn't happen in every loop
لم يحدث ذلك في كل حلقة
and it didn't cause the loop.
ولم تسبب الحلقة.
But it proves
لكن هذا يثبت
someone wants to kill you in every loop.
شخص ما يريد قتلك في كل حلقة.
The elevator of my apartment...
مصعد شقتي ...
And the car crash yesterday.
وتحطم السيارة أمس.
Someone wants to kill me?
شخص ما يريد قتلي؟
Yeah.
نعم.
According to the limitless genre,
حسب النوع اللامحدود ،
the key to ending the loop is to find the murderer.
مفتاح إنهاء الحلقة هو العثور على القاتل.
But...
ولكن...
I'm a much-loved man.
أنا رجل محبوب للغاية.
Who would like to kill me?
من يود قتلي؟
A lot of people.
الكثير من الناس.
All right, Mr. Wang.
حسنًا ، سيد وانغ.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
As long as I work here, your project will succeed.
طالما أعمل هنا ، سينجح مشروعك.
It must be him. After he's fired, he hates me.
يجب أن يكون هو.  بعد طرده ، يكرهني.
So, he wants to kill me.
لذا فهو يريد قتلي.
Wrong.
خاطئ - ظلم - يظلم.
In the last loop, you didn't fire him.
في الحلقة الأخيرة ، لم تطرده.
He doesn't have a motive.
ليس لديه دافع.
Then who else could it be?
ثم من يمكن أن يكون؟
Oh, I know. It's Chubby.
اه انا اعرف.  إنه ممتلئ.
Why does he want to kill me?
لماذا يريد قتلي؟
(Because you...)
(لأنك ...)
The first bubble tea in summer.
أول فقاعات شاي في الصيف.
The calorie of bubble tea is 500.
السعرات الحرارية للشاي الفقاعي هي 500.
Based on your basal metabolism,
بناءً على التمثيل الغذائي الأساسي الخاص بك ،
you can't burn off these calories until you run for an hour.
لا يمكنك حرق هذه السعرات الحرارية حتى تجري لمدة ساعة.
Are you sure you'll still drink it?
هل أنت متأكد أنك ستظل تشربه؟
Kill me for bubble tea?
اقتلني من أجل شاي الفقاعات؟
And you know he has a fatty liver disease?
وهل تعلم أنه مصاب بمرض الكبد الدهني؟
Then Feifei wants to kill you most.
ثم يريد Feifei قتلك أكثر.
She feels the cold most.
هي تشعر بالبرودة أكثر من غيرها.
I lower the temperature of air conditioners just to warn you.
أقوم بتخفيض درجة حرارة مكيفات الهواء فقط لتحذيرك.
But why?
لكن لماذا؟
I want you to wear long skirts at work.
أريدك أن ترتدي تنانير طويلة في العمل.
When you wear short skirts,
عندما ترتدين التنانير القصيرة ،
others keep staring at you.
يستمر الآخرون في التحديق فيك.
It seriously affects work efficiency.
يؤثر بشكل خطير على كفاءة العمل.
They two are suspicious, too.
وهما مريبان أيضا.
Good.
جيد.
Today, you've learned more than others.
لقد تعلمت اليوم أكثر من غيرك.
So much for today.
كثيرا لهذا اليوم.
It's a quarter past eleven.
انها 11:15.
You can catch the last metro.
يمكنك اللحاق بالمترو الأخير.
I deliberately let them leave
تركتهم يغادرون عمدا
before the last metro.
قبل المترو الأخير.
Isn't it sweet?
أليست حلوة؟
What's the problem?
ما هي المشكلة؟
According to our rule, if anyone works overtime till midnight,
وفقًا لقواعدنا ، إذا عمل أي شخص ساعات إضافية حتى منتصف الليل ،
he can claim the taxi fare
يمكنه المطالبة بأجرة التاكسي
and be one hour late the next morning.
وتتأخر ساعة في صباح اليوم التالي.
But what have you done?
لكن ماذا فعلت؟
Every day, you let them leave at half past eleven.
كل يوم ، تتركهم يغادرون في الساعة الحادية عشرة والنصف.
That's quite close.
هذا قريب جدًا.
Looks like
يشبه
everyone in our company has the motive to kill you.
كل شخص في شركتنا لديه الدافع لقتلك.
It's understandable. You're so annoying.
هذا مفهوم.  انت مزعج جدا.
It's normal that people want to kill you.
من الطبيعي أن يريد الناس قتلك.
Secretary Bai.
سكرتير باي.
In this case,
في هذه الحالة،
I think you have the biggest motive.
أعتقد أن لديك الدافع الأكبر.
I... I...
أنا ... أنا ...
How's that possible?
كيف هذا ممكن؟
Every time you're in trouble,
في كل مرة تكون في ورطة ،
I'm there with you.
أنا هناك معك.
What if you want to die with me?
ماذا لو كنت تريد أن تموت معي؟
Mr. Jin, Secretary Bai,
السيد جين ، السكرتير باي ،
what are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Observing secretly.
المراقبة سرا.
Got it.
فهمتك.
I went to a good restaurant
ذهبت إلى مطعم جيد
named France.
اسمه فرنسا.
Shall we have dinner there together?
هل سنتناول العشاء هناك سويًا؟
Zhe, what a big dinner!
زهي ، يا له من عشاء كبير!
Wait.
انتظر.
Chu Zhe is fishy, too.
تشو زهي مريب أيضًا.
Why?
لماذا ا؟
He's only an intern.
إنه مجرد متدرب.
But he invited me to a French restaurant whose per capita charge is 5,000.
لكنه دعاني إلى مطعم فرنسي تبلغ تكلفة الفرد فيه 5000.
And his motorcycle is worth hundreds of thousands.
وتبلغ قيمة دراجته النارية مئات الآلاف.
He...
هو...
He invited you to dinner?
هل دعاك لتناول العشاء؟
Nearly in every loop.
تقريبًا في كل حلقة.
How many times has he invited you?
كم مرة دعاك؟
Not many times.
ليس عدة مرات.
But I'll invite him to dinner tonight
لكنني سأدعوه لتناول العشاء الليلة
and sound him out.
وصوته.
Zhe.
زهي.
Check out a man for me.
تحقق من الرجل من أجلي.
(When I look closer, I see him wearing all designer clothes.)
(عندما أنظر عن كثب ، أراه يرتدي جميع ملابس المصممين).
Secretary Bai,
سكرتير باي ،
even if you didn't invite me to dinner,
حتى لو لم تدعوني للعشاء ،
I would invite you.
أود دعوتك.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
You know?
أنت تعرف؟
So, you know I...?
أنت تعرف أنني ...؟
Boss.
رئيس.
Tell us.
أخبرنا.
Why do you work in my company?
لماذا تعمل في شركتي؟
Chu Zhe. Mr. Chu Tian's son.
تشو زهي ابن السيد تشو تيان.
=I Want to Resign Every Single Day=
= أريد أن أستقيل كل يوم =
(The right of communication through network exclusively belongs to Tencent.)
(يعود حق الاتصال عبر الشبكة حصريًا إلى Tencent.)